http://www.preformed.on.ca/privacy-policy-and-terms-of-use

Skip to main content
HomeOpen menuIndustriesEnergy ProductsProduct InformationPole Line HardwareCommunication ProductsProduct InformationFeatured ProductsSpecial IndustriesAbout UsAODO Accessibility PlanInternational OperationsInvestor RelationsSupport & ContactOnline InventoryProducts
Energy Products
Product InformationPole Line Hardware
Communication Products
Product InformationFeatured ProductsSpecial IndustriesPrivacy Policy and Terms of UsePoliciesINTERNET PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USEwww.preformed.on.ca (the “Site”) is owned and operated by Preformed Line Products Company. It is our policy to comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws. This Internet Privacy Policy and Terms of Use (“Policy”) describes your rights and obligations in using this Site, as well as how we protect your privacy when we collect personal information from you. By using the Site, you agree to the terms herein, including the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, then do not use the Site. Upon our belief that your conduct fails to conform with the Policy, we, in our sole discretion and without notice, reserve the right to block your access to this Site, to investigate and to involve and cooperate with law enforcement authorities, and to pursue a civil action or criminal prosecution for any alleged or actual illegal activities involving this Site.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change the terms of this Policy. Since any changes will be posted on this page, we encourage you to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.
Information We Collect And How We Use It
We do not collect any personally identifiable information from you (e.g., name, address, telephone number, email address) unless you voluntarily choose to submit or otherwise disclose such information to us, including information submitted or disclosed by mail, telephone, fax or electronically. When you voluntarily submit information, it constitutes your consent to the use of the information for the purposes stated. We will only use your information to respond to your request for information, and will not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries. When we do so, these entities will use your information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected and to which you consented, and only as permitted under this Policy.
PLP web sites track information about the visits to those sites. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to a site, the daily requests received for particular files on a site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to customize our web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.
There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Certain PLP sites may use cookies so that we can better serve site users. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
We have no obligation to monitor the Site or the use of the Site, or to retain the content of any user session. However, we reserve the right at all times to monitor, review, retain, and/or disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request or to cooperate with law enforcement and other authorities in investigating a claim of illegal activity. We may use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to protect our service, Site, clients, potential clients, and others.
Protection of Your Information
Protecting your information is important to us. We use the industry standard technology to protect the security of your information. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or any information provided online, and you do so at your own risk. We will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. However, once we receive your transmission, we do our best to ensure its security on our systems by making reasonable efforts to protect the information.
Use of Site
Subject to the Terms set forth herein, PLP grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right to access, use and display this site and the materials thereon. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the site in any way. We authorize you to view, copy and/or download the materials from its web site only for your personal, non-commercial use, provided that you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the original materials on any copies of the materials. You may not modify the materials on the Site in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose. Any use of these materials on any other web sites or networked computer environment for any purpose is strictly prohibited. The materials on the Site are copyrighted; and any unauthorized use of the materials may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws. If you breach any of the terms of the Policy, your authorization to use this web site automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any downloaded, copies and/or printed materials.
Disclaimer
THE MATERIALS MAY CONTAIN INACCURACIES AND TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. PLP DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE MATERIALS OR THE RELIABILITY OF ANY ADVICE, OPINION, STATEMENT OR OTHER INFORMATION DISPLAYED OR DISTRIBUTED THROUGH THE SITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ANY RELIANCE ON ANY SUCH OPINION, ADVICE, STATEMENT, MEMORANDUM, OR INFORMATION SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. PLP RESERVES THE RIGHT, IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION, TO CORRECT ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY PORTION OF THE SITE. PLP MAY MAKE ANY OTHER CHANGES TO THE SITE, THE MATERIALS AND THE PRODUCTS, PROGRAMS, SERVICES OR PRICES (IF ANY) DESCRIBED IN THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
THIS SITE AND THE INFORMATION AND MATERIALS ON THE SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW FOR THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Indemnity and Limitations of Damages
You shall indemnify and hold harmless PLP, its officers, directors, shareholders, subsidiaries, and employees from and against any and all costs, damages, liabilities, and expenses (including attorneys' fees) incurred in relation to, arising from, or for the purpose of avoiding, any claim or demand from a third party that your use of the Site violates any applicable law or regulation, or the rights of any third party.
IN NO EVENT SHALL PLP OR ANY OF ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, SHAREHOLDERS, SUBSIDIARIES, OR EMPLOYEES BE LIABLE TO ANY ENTITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF INFORMATION OR PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM) THAT ARE RELATED TO THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE CONTENT, MATERIALS, AND FUNCTIONS OF THE SITE OR ANY LINKED WEBSITE, EVEN IF PLP IS EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
International Users and Choice of Law
This Site is operated and administered from within the United States of America. If you access this Site from a location outside of the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. This Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Ohio, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions. You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of the courts located in the State of Ohio, for the resolution of all disputes arising from or related to these terms and/or your use of the Site.
This Policy constitutes the entire agreement between PLP and you with respect to your use of the Site. Any cause of action you may have with respect to your use of the Site must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of the Policy or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to affect the intent of the Policy, and the remainder of this Policy shall continue in full force and effect.
Contact Us
Please contact us with any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy:
Preformed Line Products (Canada) Limited
1711 Bishop St.
Cambridge, ON, N1T 1N5
Phone: 519-740-6666
Fax: 519-740-7917
© 2020
Preformed Line Products (Canada) Limited. All rights reserved
|
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
